You
There's no reason to be surprised. This was expected. It's only natural that I am the one still standing
And they're the ones who fell before me like insects. You're fools if you expected something else
Welcome to harsh reality, children. There are no surprises here. Also, there is no fear
A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body
Kishin Asherah, I hope you're ready. Your soul is mine
You're a persistent one, aren't you? Returning to sanity after being devoured by the black blood
What's wrong? You're trembling. Are you afraid? Oh, yes. I think you're terrified
Everything wrong in this world is rooted in fear
Frustration, failure, betrayal, anger, tragedy, and of course, utter defeat
Stop talking. You don't have to hide it
Poor girl
Shut up!
Yelling won't get you anywhere. I'm not afraid of you
But you are very afraid of me indeed
Thanks to that, I'll win this battle easily
Say whatever you want
It won't change anything
She isn't shaking now
She's ready to face him
I am going to fight you
And I'll win
Let's do this
Let's go, soul residents
The Kishin hasn't made a move yet
Find your cats and hit them hard
You're so weak
My final opponent and you're nothing more than a pathetic little girl
What a shame
Maka, get up now
Your little friends were so much stronger than you
And look how they ended up
Move, Maka
You're getting up?
I think I prefer you on the ground
That position suits a little weakling like you
But I can kill you standing, too
Can you make it?
Of course I can
Let's go
If this lasts too long, I'll lose
I have to find an opening and strike
As hard as I can
Only one thing will work
She's right
We can only use one technique
And that's
Genie hunter
The anti-magic wavelength
An incredibly powerful move handed down to her from her mother
The force that can erase evil
Removing impurities until only good remains
Here she comes
She's fighting the Kishin
He's no ordinary opponent
He won't be beaten so easily
Dammit
My daughter's down there risking her life
And I can't do anything
Maka
Please
Come back to me alive
Now is our chance
This is it, Maka
Let's go
Kishin hunter
A move that targets evil
But let me ask you one thing
Am I truly evil?
If you think I am, you're wrong
The madness within me that frightens you so much isn't evil
It's normal
Everybody in this world has a trace of insanity resting within them
Even you
Madness makes no exceptions
Screw you
What a foul mouth
I'll have to punish you for that
A sweet gesture
But how futile
Sol
Are you okay?
Sol!
They all sacrificed themselves for you
But in the end, is that truly a kindness?
They've only moved the responsibility onto your shoulders
They've left you the fear of failure
Just shut the hell up
But that isn't all, is it?
There's the fear of death, too
I thought I told you to shut the hell up!
The fear of loneliness
We can't forget that
And also
The fear of pain
A primitive fear, all right
But a cruel one, nonetheless
Besides
It's effective enough against someone like you
A weak little human
How can we be sure it's still going on?
If something had happened to the Kishin, we'd know
The barrier he established would start to fade
For now we wait
And trust Maka to use her technique to destroy the Kishin
You're wrong
That's not what she needs
Maka's strength
Doesn't come from some technique
Yes
You're right
I am a weak human
But this pain
I felt worse than this before
Much, much worse than this
This pain is nothing!
Let's see how much pain you can handle then
You can dodge this
But if you do, your friend will die
That should finish it
Back up on your feet again, huh?
Well, that won't last long
What the?
Impossible
What magic is this?
What did you do?
I see, so that's what happened
This girl is a weapon
No, it's something else
She's a meister, alright
But she also has weapon blood
Why did the weapon within her not awake till now?
There's no trace of the fear she felt before
Why not?
Oh, now I see
She's remaining unconscious so she won't feel fear
She summons the weapons without knowing it
Now that I understand, I can beat her
This is a trick
I know how to fight
Come here, girl
Now I gotcha
Go on and stab me
Go on and stab me, I'm not afraid of pain
Pain
Not at all
But what about you?
Time to wake up
Fighting while your mind sleeps
That's not fair
There we go
That's much better
That suffocating feeling you have now
That's fear
You can let go now
That's enough
Let the madness carry you away
And you'll be free from all fear and pain
Let go and everything you feel now will evaporate
There's nothing more you can do here
Your friends have fallen
Your big move failed
There's no point in continuing now
Everything you've done was for nothing
You have no partner to stand beside you
Your body is weak, bruised and beaten
There's nothing you can do now to defeat me
You have nothing left
I have nothing left
Yes, that's right
You have nothing, nothing at all
And I'll be alright then
I don't understand what you're saying
Is there something else she can use besides the anti-magic wavelength?
Some other technique?
Like I said
Her greatest strength isn't a technique
It's something different
Something in here
Krona is right about that
Look who's awake
I'm back, baby
I'm still as eloquent as ever, I see
What?
What did you say?
Didn't you hear me?
I said it's going to be alright
What?
No it won't
Alright!
The genie hunter isn't what I need to defeat you
I went along with what the teacher said
I thought that move was my only hope
They were wrong
That isn't my greatest power
Not at all
What are you saying?
You little fool
Maka isn't the fool, you jackass
Do you all understand what I'm talking about now?
Don't you get it yet?
Maka may not be a great star like I am
But she's got something amazing, alright
Maka's strength
Isn't some special ability
It's more
It's something
That can beat fear
It's bravery
That's all bravery?
I don't understand you people
You put faith in something as fragile as one girl's bravery?
Stop it
Don't look at me like that
How can you be so calm at a time like this?
What's happening?
Who the hell are you?
I'm academy student Maka Alban
One star scythemeister
Not what I meant
I'm not asking you your name
You're standing there so calmly
That's not normal
What are you?
I'm just me
Nothing more and nothing less
She's making me nervous
But I don't understand why that is
I'm so confused
It's like the feeling you get
When you wake up from a bad dream
You can't remember
I've had enough of this
You have to die now
I'm going to kill all of you
I don't have any other time
Shujat
What?
What is that?
A postcard
With a message
But that doesn't matter
It's none of your business
None of my business?
How could you talk to me like that?
You insolent
Oh no
Whatever you're doing
Stop!
No
I won't
I've come too far to stop now
If I gave up
How could I face the people
Who have stood by me
Supported me for so long
They're the reason I'm here
They lent me their courage
Now it's time to use my own
It's time for me to be brave for them
That's ridiculous
You don't know what you're talking about
Bravery is my armor
And this is my weapon
Fool
You really think that pitiful little fist will hurt me?
You'll accomplish nothing
Why can't you see how useless it is to try?
You should have given this fight up a long time ago
I don't understand anything that's going on
I don't get it
Why do you have so much faith in her?
She's weak
She isn't special
She's nothing more than a human
What is bravery?
Kishin, are you ready?
I'm coming!
Go away!
What's the point of destroying me?
Madness won't disappear just because I'm gone
Another one will take my place
There will be a new Kishin
An heir to my madness
He will rain insanity upon the worlds of the Niacan
That's the way this world will always be
Why can't you see your struggle is pointless?
I don't care
Stay away
I will defeat you
You didn't even scratch me
Your fist wasn't enough after all
You fool
There's no way a weak, talentless little human like you could beat me
You didn't stand a chance
What is this?
You just punched me
Your fist isn't a weapon
It's nothing special
Exactly
Bravery's not special
But that means
Everybody has it
Everybody, huh?
Then it's just like madness
The barrier's gone
They did it?
Fool!
Take a look
Where's Maka?
Don't worry
My Maka's too strong to be defeated
Finally
It looks like it's over at last
You did it, Maka
You really are amazing
Coolest partner ever
The sky's all pretty now!
Well done!
We defeated the Kishin and Bad Weather!
How about that?
Ha!
We win!
The sky's blue!
I surpassed God and the Kishin
Are you okay, Sol?
Well, we finally did it
But there's still a lot of work ahead of us
Yeah, like rebuilding Death City and repairing the Academy
Well, at least we can celebrate that the Kishin's gone now, right?
We can't be too happy
People still inhabit this world
There will always be more evil to face
We were able to scrape through this time because of Maka
But sooner or later another Kishin will rise up
It'll be okay
When it does come
We'll be there
Besides
There's a lot more to people than evil thoughts and bad deeds
There's bravery
Everybody has that
Right in here
Kuzu-boshi
Kira-me-ku
Yume-no
Hoshisah
I wanna be
I wanna take my heart
世界は黒って染まってる
吐く息は白いままなのに
今をぶっ壊しにいこうって約束したあの日から
きっとまだ間に合うはずだから
I wanna be here
ges stick up
Help me feel here
I'm you here
A little baby
Who will it be?
What is it?
I'm you here
Help me feel here
I'm here
I wanna be here
Oh
I wanna be
聞こえてるか
ずっとここにいるよ
ご視聴ありがとうございました